xtendedview.com 2019-05-06

# Privacy Policy: www.xtendedview.com

**Privacy Policy for xtendedview.com**  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at tushar[at]xtendedview.com or you can use this page to [contact us](http://xtendedview.com/contact-us/).

Here, the privacy of your information is important and the below are the details of what kind of data is collected from you and how it is stored. Your personal data will never be sold to third parties.

**Log Files**

The information on logs include few details of your IP address, ISP- (Internet Service Provider), Browser Name, your browsing habits and the kind of information you love to read here and also the time and pages you visited.

**Cookies and History:**

The cookies are used to store information like your time of stay, personal data you provide in comment section. As you might have noticed, few third party advertisements are also used on this site which may use cookies and web beacons which are needed for them to collect some information like your IP address, ISP, browser and in some cases if you have flash installed to run flash ads. Also there are website performance and stat tracking tools used here which collect few information as discussed above. These details are used so as to present you with a relevant kind of ad which you would like to browse through.

You may disable cookies on your browser but it affects your interaction with this site.

**Advertising and Privacy:**

We use Google Adsense as the major advertising network. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). You may read more about Adsense privacy policies [here](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=100557).

**Interest Based Advertising:**

Google Adsense will soon start serving ads based on the interest of the user/visitor. If you visit sports related sites very regularly which uses adsense, then you will be grouped into “sports enthusiast” category. This is called [Interest based advertising](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=113771) and to achieve this, they collect some data from visitos which do not include your name, mail id, phone number, address or any such details. You may read more about it [here](http://adsense.blogspot.com/2009/03/driving-monetization-with-ads-that.html).

**Comment and Contact:**

We collect your name and email id in the comment section and also the contact form. This information will be used only to contact you in any case of need which may occur. That will only be used to make new announcements or sometimes to reply your queries. The information collected at the comment section and contact form is totally safe and will not be disclosed to anyone.
